<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; KoLee Networking Formerly IKHNetworks</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/station-news/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Daring To Make A Difference</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:34:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/cropped-cropped-KoLeeLogo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; KoLee Networking Formerly IKHNetworks</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Rosalind, Exchange @ 104 &#038; 278 North Macy St Outages</title>
		<link>/rosalind-exchange-104-with-no-tv-278-north-macy-st/</link>
					<comments>/rosalind-exchange-104-with-no-tv-278-north-macy-st/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=952</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hi There If You Are Seeing This Message &#8211; You may be a victim of the current on going outage for a few weeks now. Now let&#8217;s get down to brass tax. If you are a resident here and can&#8217;t get TV, or internet &#8211; it&#8217;s because of contract and leasing disputes. This incident was...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hi There If You Are Seeing This Message &#8211; You may be a victim of the current on going outage for a few weeks now. Now let&#8217;s get down to brass tax. </p>



<p>If you are a resident here and can&#8217;t get TV, or internet &#8211; it&#8217;s because of contract and leasing disputes. </p>



<p>This incident was directed at me and 3 other people who needed high roof access for our medical equipment, AT&amp;T and Charter did not wish to accommodate us and started ripping out all antennas without reaching out to the landlord about any life and safety services that may be on the building.</p>



<p>As a result pulled some stupid choices of their own. </p>



<p>In the case of the Rosalind, the dispute got so ugly that they took 3 dumpster loads of antennas off the property including repeaters for medical equipment. </p>



<p>In that process their own &#8220;contracted&#8221; housing authority engineer cut wires for the residents to use internet or TV. </p>



<p>There&#8217;s a way around this bullshit outage and let&#8217;s showcase that &#8211; number 1 &#8211; T-Mobile home internet or US Cellular home internet. </p>



<p>If you are at the 3rd story or higher get an indoor antenna <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Channel-Master-Omni-CM-3011HD-Omnidirectional/dp/B07T25NFHK/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.amazon.com/Channel-Master-Omni-CM-3011HD-Omnidirectional/dp/B07T25NFHK/">I recommend this antenna </a> (it&#8217;s 80$ on amazon) if you have a stereo and wish to get great radio reception so you can blast great tunes at your parties you&#8217;ll want <a href="https://www.amazon.com/RCA-Amplified-Indoor-HDTV-Antenna/dp/B000HKGK9I/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.amazon.com/RCA-Amplified-Indoor-HDTV-Antenna/dp/B000HKGK9I/">this antenna</a> (it&#8217;s 34$) on amazon and I&#8217;ve used this antenna just to listen to my own station and it&#8217;s really good at what it does. </p>



<p>Why this is key no matter what. </p>



<p>This will actually be better than sharing the same antenna and internet connections with all other stories in your building. The internet is like water hoses, the more connected to the building supplied internet, the more slow it will be &#8211; there&#8217;s only so much that can go around in a 10 or 8 story building.</p>



<p>Even after repairs I still would keep your antenna and internet private continue to use US Cellular or T-Mobile home internet and your own antenna if you wish to continue to get TV. </p>



<p>Regardless it will take months to repair knowing the housing authority contractors and the backlog they have for repairs. </p>



<p>Please be kind, show them respect, and patience. They are overworked and have next to no staff. In the case of Exchange @ 104, they have no staff running this building for a few months on end and have a regional district president here coming from Ohio / Indiana.  </p>



<p>The Arc 278 North Macy Street Address is experiencing their own outage for months on end due to upgrades. It&#8217;s been witnessed by the Blue Greyhound News Team who saw alliant energy over by the Lutheran Home along with Spectrum vehicles and AT&amp;T, actually removing the poles and moving utilities underground. </p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/rosalind-exchange-104-with-no-tv-278-north-macy-st/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FCC Licensing</title>
		<link>/fcc-licensing/</link>
					<comments>/fcc-licensing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 03:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-embed-pdf-viewer-pdf wp-block-embed-pdf-viewer-pdf__content-wrapper aligncenter alignundefined"><object class="embed-pdf-viewer" data="/wp-content/uploads/STL.pdf#scrollbar=1&amp;toolbar=1" type="application/pdf" height="784" width="784" title=""></object><iframe class="embed-pdf-viewer" src="https://docs.google.com/viewer?url=%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2FSTL.pdf&amp;embedded=true" frameborder="0" height="784" width="784" title=""></iframe></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-pdf-viewer-pdf wp-block-embed-pdf-viewer-pdf__content-wrapper aligncenter alignundefined"><object class="embed-pdf-viewer" data="/wp-content/uploads/Repeaters.pdf#scrollbar=1&amp;toolbar=1" type="application/pdf" height="790" width="790" title=""></object><iframe loading="lazy" class="embed-pdf-viewer" src="https://docs.google.com/viewer?url=%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2FRepeaters.pdf&amp;embedded=true" frameborder="0" height="790" width="790" title=""></iframe></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/fcc-licensing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon Closed All Holiday Long</title>
		<link>/waupun-alto-brandon-ripon-closed-all-december/</link>
					<comments>/waupun-alto-brandon-ripon-closed-all-december/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 11:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Missing Some Stations This Morning, You might be if you live, work or play in Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon. No further information is available other than &#8211; we want to avoid the city of Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon, getting free and highly illegal access to the city of Fond Du Lac light show as a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<p class="has-text-align-left has-medium-font-size">Missing Some Stations This Morning, You might be if you live, work or play in Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon. </p>



<p class="has-text-align-left has-medium-font-size">No further information is available other than &#8211; we want to avoid the city of Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon, getting free and highly illegal access to the city of Fond Du Lac light show as a result of transmitter changes that would violate the FCC rules by reducing the power &#8211; out of respect for the FDL light show. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">Since &#8211; 87.9 FM will reduce its&#8217;s power against professional advice so you can enjoy the light show at Lakeside Park. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">By doing this we have shutdown Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon transmitters because they are fed via a daisy chain this means non fond du lac residents will hear the lakeside park light show in Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon, which would be highly illegal. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">It&#8217;s free for Fond Du Lac residence &#8211; not sure and not willing to take the risk of accidentally simulcasting an unlicensed christmas light show to non residence. I can and will allow this very serious confusion to remain in Fond Du Lac. As you&#8217;ll also hear the light show in Fond Du Lac on 96.7 FM due to the upcoming accident caused by the city. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">But it not for Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon transmitters which would be fed the light show audio because of an accident that will be very clear during the holiday season. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">The daisy chain setup 87.9 FM feeds, 92.7 FM, 92.7 FM feeds 96.7 FM, and 96.7 FM feeds 97.7 FM (HD2), 97.7 FM HD2 feeds 98.3 FM, and 98.3 FM feeds 102.5 FM. </p>



<p></p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">With this setup you hear the exact same thing as 87.9 FM this means the light show will be available to Fond Du Lac will be heard on all repeaters. Including Fond Du Lac, and even more confusing Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">Since sadly &#8211; the lakeside park light show would cause harmful interference to the licensed operations of 87.9 FM. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">We&#8217;ve closed down repeaters and yes that includes my crisis plans are halted for me for me in Fond Du Lac, Waupun, Alto, Brandon, Ripon &#8211; all holiday long. </p>



<p class="has-medium-font-size">Despite doing against professional advice means that by not shutting down Waupun, Alto Brandon, and Ripon transmitters, it means that Fond Du Lac lakeside park audio would be heard on 92.7 FM Ripon, 98.3 FM Alto / Brandon and 102.5 FM Waupun regardless it&#8217;s a confusing mess this year. Be safe &#8211; The Twisted Lion King Morning Show. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/waupun-alto-brandon-ripon-closed-all-december/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tornado Warning Blunder &#038; US Marshals</title>
		<link>/tornado-warning-blunder-us-marshals/</link>
					<comments>/tornado-warning-blunder-us-marshals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=906</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The national weather service issued a tornado warning for all of South Eastern Wisconsin last night starting at 7 PM and finally let it expire at 9:30 &#8211; the worst part of this blunder &#8211; is there was no tornado threat &#8211; instead human error &#8211; someone in the weather service office had actually pushed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<p>The national weather service issued a tornado warning for all of South Eastern Wisconsin last night starting at 7 PM and finally let it expire at 9:30 &#8211; the worst part of this blunder &#8211; is there was no tornado threat &#8211; instead human error &#8211; someone in the weather service office had actually pushed the wrong button. Causing us to begin operating W65BT (TV 65 and even 87.9 FM in emergency mode &#8211; including watching the skies around FDL and reading the national weather service weather script &#8211; endlessly. </p>



<p>The other thing that was part of the big blunder is that if this was activated in a manner that was not human error &#8211; the tornado sirens are not working. This is why everyone should have multiple ways to get weather alerts.</p>



<p>It took the national weather service 2 hours to actually pull the faux pas. The mess wasn&#8217;t cleaned up, false alarm and program wasn&#8217;t allowed to return until the EOM tones &#8211; issued for stations to stop reading the tornado safety script like me doing last night on main street. The national weather service finally let the blunder die by getting superiors to pull it at 9:30 PM. </p>



<p>Likewise while I was actually going past Macy Street &#8211; I happened to come across police activity &#8211; which wasn&#8217;t at that time requiring a shelter in place order &#8211; I happened to walk past on the other side &#8211; walking past Penton Counseling &#8211; my therapist &#8211; continuing the broadcast of severe weather coverage on our new almost real time livestream system. </p>



<p>Came past the main street area on Kwik Trip around 8 PM only to walk by a car accident &#8211; worse yet &#8211; about 8:20 PM &#8211; I heard shots fired &#8211; only to see the US Marshals &#8211; start asking people to go into nearby businesses or their apartments if it was within 3 to 4 blocks &#8211; because of a very deadly situation.  </p>



<p>Earlier around 7:15 PM I actually came across the heavy police presence and they had fire rescue and all police officers on duty the lady was in tears saying that something sinister was going to happen in the immediate area well happening to record at about 8:20 PM &#8211; heading back home from a walk on the bridge &#8211; I heard shots fired. </p>



<p>Heading back in that direction to go home the US Marshals it actually asked everybody to go immediately to shelter in shelter in place in the meantime you&#8217;re hearing Bob Stei who has the famous grunge garage radio show for the first time as a live simulcast on 87.9 FM it&#8217;s the first ever official simulcast of the grunge garage with Bob&#8217;s Stei and Rock&#8217;n Rhett Butler</p>



<p><a href="https://facebook.com/FDLCountyEM?__cft__[0]=AZUxcc7BdcvD8w2q7ax8TKh-pSCdlUBn9YFfWBRDnCNivi2YG1qRiLbKgPKfh-QuevQJdCkL7GFzdLVcZqhJBLyi-_iCE-usq2zIZxanLX50zA8a5Z-z8vJueTGhFwGMnexClpfTDM32V5r-CyyrIe5VqLrje2-z95Dh28pOhvaM_w&amp;__tn__=H-R" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/tornado-warning-blunder-us-marshals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 Year Anniversary of Retro Rock</title>
		<link>/2-year-anniversary-of-retro-rock/</link>
					<comments>/2-year-anniversary-of-retro-rock/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=898</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Retro Rock celebrates it&#8217;s 2 years on the air &#8211; we have been with Retro Rock for almost one year &#8211; actually come to think about it &#8211; September 3rd is my one year anniversary with Retro Rock. Also should make sure to let people know &#8211; including Rhett as well &#8211; we are on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="388" height="304" src="/wp-content/uploads/image002.png" alt="" class="wp-image-899"/></figure></div>


<p>Retro Rock celebrates it&#8217;s 2 years on the air &#8211; we have been with Retro Rock for almost one year &#8211; actually come to think about it &#8211; September 3rd is my one year anniversary with Retro Rock. Also should make sure to let people know &#8211; including Rhett as well &#8211; we are on our forever home of 87.9 FM. We have had many stations over the years but finally was able to settle to just one AM &amp; FM station &#8211; 87.9 FM &amp; 660 AM- it&#8217;s call letters are WNBC during the daytime and during the night time it uses the call letters WPLJ as an FCC approved bypass to the daytime only rules. </p>



<p>You can listen to Retro Rock rewind Monday through Thursday on KoLee Networking stations including 87.9 FM and 660 AM. Likewise you can also<a href="http://www.webrockrevolution.net/" data-type="URL" data-id="www.webrockrevolution.net"> listen online</a></p>



<p>We also simulcast Grunge Garage from 8 PM to 12 AM on our station on Sundays. </p>



<p>Congratulations on 2 years Rockin&#8217; Rhett and Bob Stei </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2-year-anniversary-of-retro-rock/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thrive Church &#038; National EAS Test</title>
		<link>/thrive-church-national-eas-test/</link>
					<comments>/thrive-church-national-eas-test/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=892</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[National EAS Test is set to take place at exactly 9:20 AM this morning &#8211; National EAS test is set to be exclusive to Blue Greyhound stations a service of lockheed martin. It will use the script from the 2018 national EAS test. Only 48 stations are involved with this test. You can listen to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>National EAS Test is set to take place at exactly 9:20 AM this morning &#8211; National EAS test is set to be exclusive to Blue Greyhound stations a service of lockheed martin. It will use the script from the 2018 national EAS test. Only 48 stations are involved with this test. </p>



<p>You can listen to Thrive Church Today right here on 87.9 FM and some radios on 87.7 FM and 660 AM and also TV 65 </p>



<p>You can also listen at this player below &#8211; our actual live broadcast feed. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-audio"><audio controls src="https://livestream.kolee.net/live"></audio></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/thrive-church-national-eas-test/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Car Accident By 160 Macy St &#8211; Saturday Aug 27 2022 &#8211; 9:30 PM</title>
		<link>/car-accident-by-160-macy-st-saturday-aug-27-2022-930-pm/</link>
					<comments>/car-accident-by-160-macy-st-saturday-aug-27-2022-930-pm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 03:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=888</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Late Breaking News &#8211; 9:30 PM &#8211; August 27th 2022 &#8211; A car accident involving a female white SUV and black pickup truck in front of 160 S Macy Street in Fond Du Lac. Due to this being a very recent event &#8211; there&#8217;s no media release at this time &#8211; so no injuries are...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Late Breaking News &#8211; 9:30 PM &#8211; August 27th 2022 &#8211; A car accident involving a female white SUV and black pickup truck in front of 160 S Macy Street in Fond Du Lac.</p>



<p>Due to this being a very recent event &#8211; there&#8217;s no media release at this time &#8211;<s> so no injuries are documented for public knowledge</s>.</p>



<p>Update at 4:40 AM &#8211; updates on this accident include injuries and also include transportation to SSM hospital for one of the vehicle operators. (The operator in the black truck).  </p>



<p>Is it&#8217;s now under investigation.</p>



<p>This is in front of the 8th story building from Exchange at 104 &#8211; we&#8217;re our transmitter is &#8211; and most notably our apartment too &#8211; granted on the 7th floor.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter"><img decoding="async" src="https://twistedstallion.com/wp-content/uploads/PXL_20220828_023526024-scaled.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-688"/></figure></div>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/car-accident-by-160-macy-st-saturday-aug-27-2022-930-pm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Box Returns</title>
		<link>/the-box-returns/</link>
					<comments>/the-box-returns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ian KoLee]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=847</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Box Music Network Returns To FDL TV sets. The First 14 minutes of The Box Music Network can be see with the video shown below this caption]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Box Music Network Returns To FDL TV sets.</p>



<p><strong>The First 14 minutes of The Box Music Network can be see with the video shown below this caption</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-video"><video controls src="https://cdn.kolee.net/Theboxreturns.m4v"></video></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-box-returns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		<enclosure url="https://cdn.kolee.net/Theboxreturns.m4v" length="103488427" type="video/mp4" />

			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
